One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Beyond the hard rain, I saw a rainbow in the sky
hageshii ame no mukou kakaru niji o mita
We know the easy answers are all lies, yeah?
tayasui kotae wa uso da to shiru daro
Swear not to lose to the loudest voices
dekai koe nanka ni makenai to chikatte
Even if you face tomorrow alone, I hope you'll understand
anata hitori ni wakatte hoshii ashita
You, who gave me the time of my life
yume no you na jikan kureta anata
What am I to you,
watashi wa dou mieteru no
an angel or a devil?
sore ga tenshi ka akuma ka
Beyond the dawn, beyond the dawn
yoake no mukou yoake no mukou
I have so much I want to tell you
hanashitai koto takusan arun da
All my love, all my love,
ai kometa ai kometa
could never fit into the letters I wrote
tegami ni kakikirenai omoi da
Those tiny palms outstretched, searching for eternity
eien o sagashita chiisana te no hira
Luffy vs. Kizaru
My...
how large you’ve become.
Whoa, there...
Here we go!
Let’s not get carried...
away...!
Look at him fly!
Hurry, let's run for it now!
Yeah, while Luffy's holding off Kizaru!
Where are you going, Atlas?!
Down below to take back control
of the pacifistas!
Otherwise...
as soon as the barrier goes down...
they’ll laser us to death!
That’s a great idea!
There's no higher authority
on this island than Vegapunk!
Whoever controls the pacifistas wins!
Yeah! I’m heading out!
Wait, Atlas!
I-I’ll go with you!
Huh?!
But you can’t go!
Why is that?
Don’t “Why” me! This whole thing is happening
because people are after your life!
But...
Hey, Franky!
Franky, do you read me?!
Yeah!
It seems like Bonney is down there!
She’s alive?! That’s great!
Kizaru kicked her right into the barrier...
Kicked, you say?!
How does a grown man like you
let her get kicked?!
Sorry, my fault!
I'll save her as soon as I can!
You’d better!
But the barrier...
Building A,
2nd Floor
This is Sanji speaking!
If Bonney needs to be rescued, count me in!
Vegapunk, we’ve grabbed
all the luggage you mentioned.
I’ll head toward the rear exit!
Let’s all meet up there!
Roger that.
Stop loitering around!
Move, move, move!
Damn it... Stay away
from the center of town!
We believe that the pirate
Jewelry Bonney is there!
She's lurking somewhere! Just watch out!
She’ll manipulate your age!
It’s heavy!
Damn... Where'd she scamper off to?
Somebody, get this off me!
Find her! She’s gotta be
around here somewhere!
Take her out!
Dammit...
Hey! Over here!
We found Sentomaru!
He’s burned to a crisp!
Sentomaru...
S-Sentomaru!
Bonney...
Run...
The Marines... are coming...
Sentomaru!
What do I do?
Found her?
No!
Sweep that way!
Yes, sir!
Can I manage to stay hidden
until it all blows over?
Labophase
Look atcha go!
Zoro! You want help?
Just focus on Kizaru!
If this is the best you can do,
don’t expect to get a chance
to go up against our captain.
Perhaps...
But an Emperor’s right-hand man...
is still well worth killing.
I seem to be falling toward the ocean...
Sacred Yasakani Jewel.
Whaaa?!
Sacred Murakumo Sword.
Yeowch!
Gum-Gum...
Dawn...
Whip!
No dice!
Was that a Hollow-Hollow?!
Which one’s the real one?!
Just kidding.
Tricked ya!
Gum-Gum...
Dawn...
Stamp!
Did I get the real one, too?
He tricked me!
How strange...
Wherever could Vegapunk be?
Mind telling me?
Luffy!
Apple Gramps!
Wait! Let me in, Vegapunk!
What's gotten into you?!
You look crazy!
Get your hands off of her,
damned Marines!
I’m on my way to save you, Bonney!
How could I leave a child like her
behind to die?!
A child?
Get in already!
You’ve got a ticket to ride!
Cram yourself in wherever!
“Cram” myself...?
That hurt...
What are you doing?!
Don't go into the open!
He'll kill you!
Where do you think you’re going...
Vegapunk?
Whoa, whoa, whoa! This isn't good, Stella!
He came back?!
Stella?!
Lilith! Use the General Franky
to carry the ship!
I'm catching this ride!
Got it!
Edison! Now!
All righty! Frontier Dome,
partially deactivate!
Reactivate!
We're falling!
This is the Fabriophase on the island!
Reporting in! Dr. Vegapunk
has descended from the Labophase!
Prepare to fire! Aim!
All pacifista units!
Vegapunk has new orders!
Wipe out...
all Marines on the island!
Wh...
What?!
That can’t be good...
Now we’re the...!
Target modified.
Eradicate sailors.
Stay away from the pacifistas!
Damn you, Vegapunk...
Did he override their orders?
Damn you, Vegapunk!
How is this things driving straight down?!
We should be in free fall!
Island clouds have the property of
attaching to each other.
The tires of this Vegatank
are made of island clouds, so it won’t fall!
Enough about that!
Atlas, search for Bonney!
She must feel terrifed, being all alone!
Bonney!
Where are you?! Bonney!
I found her!
Where is she?!
All I see are Marines!
You sure, Sanji?!
Has my radar ever been wrong?!
Well, no...
An utterly unscientific radar,
but I’m willing to trust it!
Thanks!
But this tank...
is too slow to keep up
with my impatient heart!
I’m on my way, Bonney!
Good thing...
that the pacifistas
are on our side again.
Finally found you,
Jewelry Bonney the pirate!
Marine HQ Vice Admiral
Pomsky
How could you do that to my men!
She’s over here!
N.D.E.!
Near-Death Experience
Hey! What’s wrong, men?!
I saw... the River Styx...
Get back here, Bonney!
No escape for you!
What?!
Why?!
I can control an individual
regardless of the authority hierarchy!
As a Driver with the Ride-Ride Fruit,
I can take a ride on anything!
Marine HQ Vice Admiral
Bluegrass
If I kill you, will that undo the curse
you put on our soldiers?!
Daddy...
Give back their proper ages!
You can’t space out like that, Bonney!
Black Leg!
I heard about how
Kuma’s your old man...
But you gotta be smarter
than this! Or else you’ll...
Otter Hammer!
Let’s just get outta here!
Bonney!
Get in, Sanji, Bonney!
The pacifistas are on our side now!
Let’s head back up!
Sorry, but...
spending all my time on you
would jeopardize my mission!
And that’s...
my mission!
Now this is a dilemma...
Wait up!
What’s this unearthly presence?
Stand down, pacifistas.
What’s this?!
The pacifistas stopped guarding us!
Move, pacifistas! Protect us!
Follow your orders!
What's happening?
The only ones above us
on the authority hierarchy...
are...
the Five Elders!
Enemy fire?!
A magic pentagram?!
What the...
This is weird!
Let's hurry on up!
Of course!
Alert to all units on location!
St. Saturn of the Five Elders
is disembarking on Egghead!
No one below the rank of Commodore
may behold him!
One of the Five Elders?!
I repeat!
St. Saturn of the Five Elders
is disembarking on Egghead!
What was that explosion?!
The Five Elders?! One of them
has come all the way here?!
The Five Elders?!
Who the hell are they?!
They’re the highest
authority in the world!
Say what?!
Something’s coming outta there!
What is that...?! It’s a monster!
Cut it out!
That’s gotta be...
The surface world...
Long has it been...
Highest Authority of the World Government
Five Elders - Godhead of Science & Defense
St. Jaygarcia Saturn
What is that monster?!
Up above! Watch out!
Whoops...
So close...
Oh no! The island clouds...!
Bonney!
Kizaru!
Hold it, Kizaru!
You must be reaching your
limit in that form by now...
Please, Luffy!
Do something!
Count on...
me...!
Gum-Gum...
Star...
Gun!
Well, this can’t be good!
Nika...
That's my limit...
You okay, Vegapunk?!
Nothing to worry over.
Atlas, are you hurt?!
I’m fine!
St. Saturn, I take it?
Indeed.
I thought we already had you killed, Vegapunk.
I gave you an order, Vegapunk.
Bonney!
You will not leave him any free will!
But then Kuma would...!
DADDY
St. Saturn!
Conquering the world, believing in the future
sekai o seishite mirai o shinjite
What did you see, what did you learn?
nani o mite nani o shitte
Once again, I couldn't save a soul
mata daremo mamorenai no
My fault their voices're fading away
kiekakaru koe wa boku no sei
Don't even have time to hang my head
utsumuku hima mo nai no
Gravel marks on my palms
tenohira ni tsuku jari no ato
We're setting off again, my ship!
mata ugokidase boku no fune yo
Though I can't fly in the open skies
hiroi sora wa tobenai kedo
I can light up the deep sea
fukai umi wa teraseru kara
Which is why...
bokura wa
EVERYDAY owarenai
Everyday, we can't quit
EVERYDAY makerenai
Everyday, we can't lose
We've got something right here to defend
mamoru mono ga koko ni wa aru
Were my predictions all wrong?
yosou chigai kamo
But I can't stop anymore
tomarenai yo mou
We forge on, sharing the loneliness
kodoku o ima wakeai susumu
Don't chicken out now
ojikezukuna yo
I'm nothing like I used to be
ano hi no boku to chigau kara
No one can stand in my way
dare ni mo jama dekinai yo
So move!
saa doite
Conquering the world, believing in the future,
sekai o seishite mirai o shinjite
counting the endless nights
ikutsumo no yoru kazoete
What did you see, what did you learn,
nani o mite nani o shitte
taisetsu na koto ni kizuita no
to realize what's really important?